A drug-fuelled road trip in the 60s
Magic Trip: Ken Kesey's Search for a Kool Place is a
documentary, music film directed by Alison Ellwood.
A freewheeling portrait of Ken Kesey and the Merry Prankster’s fabled
road trip across America in the legendary Magic Bus.
In 1964, Ken Kesey, the famed author of “One Flew Over the Cuckoo’s Nest,” set off on a
legendary, LSD-fuelled cross-country road trip to the New York World’s Fair.
He was joined by “The Merry Band of Pranksters,” a renegade group of counterculture truth-seekers, including Neal Cassady, the
American icon immortalized in Kerouac’s “On the Road,” and the driver and painter of the psychedelic Magic Bus.
Self, played by Ken Kesey.
Self (archive footage), played by Jerry Garcia.
Self, played by Neal Cassady.
Self (archive footage), played by Phil Lesh.
Self (archive footage), played by Bob Weir.
Ken Babbs (born January 14, 1936)  is a Merry Prankster who
became one of the psychedelic leaders of the 1960s.
He along with best friend and Prankster leader, Ken
Kesey, wrote the book Last Go Round.
Babbs is best known for his participation in the
Acid Tests and on the bus Furthur.
The film explores themes of biography, based on true
story, road trip, woman director.